Guide to the Gerard Malanga Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2006 acquisition, 1906-2005; 81.05; (102 boxes) + 2 art, 6 rolls, 4 broadside folders
  - " This Will Kill That, Photocopies of Holographs Tipped into Ltd Ed.", undated (Box 24)
  - " This Will Kill That - Part IV", undated; 3 (Box 24)
  - "Correspondence to Gerard Malanga re: MacLise Archive", 1980-1981, undated (Box 24)
  - "Ting Pa Magazine Edited by A. MacLise", 1976, undated (Box 24)
  - "Angus MacLise DIA Art FDN. Photocopies of Original Holographs + Typescripts", undated; 2 (Box 24)
  - "Angus MacLise - Horoscope", undated (Box 24)
  - "Velimir Khlebnikov Translation Project. Paul Schmidt + Jake HIrschman", 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard - Miscellaneous", 1966, undated (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard / Steven Hall, The Poetry Project, Post Card Invitation", 1997, undated (Box 24)
  - "Contract Draft / Rene Ricard", 1978 September 19 (Box 24)
  - "Correspondence Referring to Rene Ricard", 1977-1980, undated (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard / DIA Art Foundation Key Players - Correspondence", 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard", 1977-1979, undated (Box 24)
  - "Delia Doherty (A Thumbnail Sketch in Jungle Red) by Rene Ricard, Jan. 5, 1976", 1976 January 5 (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard - Tearsheets", 1978-1980, undated (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard / 1st Clean Draft Typescript", 1966-1978, undated (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard - 1st Variant", 1966-1978, undated (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard 42-pg Sheaf of Mostly Uncollected Poems", 1965-1971, undated (Box 24)
  - "Rene Ricard 103-pg Sheaf of Assorted / Mostly Uncollected Poems", 1978, undated (Box 24)
  - "Dia Art FDN - Memos, etc.", 1981, undated (Box 24)
  - "The Publishing Program of Dia Art FDN as Outlined by Malanga", 1979-1990 (Box 24)
  - Journal, undated (Box 24)
  - "Re: Rene Ricard Letters", 1976 (Box 25)
  - Heiner Freidrich, undated (Box 25)
  - "Rene Ricard: Poems Excluded from His First Book with DIA", 1965-1978, undated (Box 25)
  - "Accounts Tracking Folder / Rene Ricard", 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - "Rene Ricard: Typescript 2nd Variant", undated (Box 25)
  - "Samples", undated (Box 25)
  - "MSS - Unpub. + Published", 1971, undated (Box 25)
  - "Rene Ricard / Completed Book / Tiffany Catalog Prototype", 1977-1979, undated (Box 25)
  - "Rene Ricard / DIA Art FDN - Supplementary Correspondence", 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - "Rene Ricard Published Works", 1973-1990; 2 (Box 25)
  - "Tony Conrad Tape Collection", 1980; 2 (Box 25)
  - "Angus MacLise: Application Accepted by CAPS", 1974 March 8 (Box 25)
  - "Angus MacLise: Guggenheim Reccomendation by La Monte Young", 1978-1987 (Box 25)
  - "Labels for Tape Index", undated (Box 25)
  - "MacLise Tapes in La Monte Young's Collection", 1963-1980 (Box 25)
  - "Correspondence Received by Gerard Malanga. Angus MacLise Archive / DIA Art FDN", 1980-1982; 2 (Box 25)
  - "Hetty MacLise. Angus MacLise Archive / DIA Art Fdn.", 1979-1984 (Box 25)
  - "Angus MacLise. Gerard Malanga Carbon Replies...", 1979-1982, undated (Box 25)
  - "Progress Reports 1 thru 5, 2/22/79 thru 12/13/79", 1979, undated (Box 25)
  - "Rene Ricard 1979-1980. Public Relations and Various Components to the Book's Evolution", 1978-1980 (Box 25)
  - "Angus MacLise / Book Publisher Solicitations and Responses from Receipt of MacLise Checklist", 1981 (Box 25)
  - "MacLise / Biographical Data and Chronologies", undated (Box 25)
  - "Don Snyder", 1980 (Box 25)
  - "MacLise Checklist / Master Copy", undated (Box 25)
  - "Checklist. Angus MacLise Collection. Compiled by Gerard Malanga", 1980-1981 (Box 25)
  - "Ira Cohen Collection", 1969, undated (Box 26)
  - "Angus MacLise - Mss", 1973, undated (Box 26)
  - "(MacLise) Contract, Extensions Correspondence", 1980-1981 (Box 26)
  - "Notes by Malanga / on MacLise", 1981, undated (Box 26)
  - "GM Letters to Angus MacLise. Angus MacLise to Don Snyder", 1979, undated (Box 26)
  - "Book Review / Performance Announcements", 1970, undated (Box 26)
  - "Invoices - Paid / Unpaid", 1980-1981 (Box 26)
  - "Paul Bang - Log Book", 1980 (Box 26)
  - "Audio Tape Inventory. Tapes Copied by Don Snyder", undated (Box 26)
  - "Tearsheets. Angus MacLise Archive", 1980-1981, undated (Box 26)
  - "John Lennon Tearsheets. Angus MacLise Archive", 1980-1981, undated (Box 26)
  - "Angus MacLise - Project Analysis / DIA Art Fdn.", 1979-1981 (Box 26)
  - "David Rattray: 'The Darkened Chamber' Essay", undated (Box 26)
  - "David Rattray Correspondence + Mss", 1979-1983 (Box 26)
  - "David Rattray Trans. Antonin Artaud", 1983 (Box 26)
  - "Diane Hersey / Son Cannon; Daughter Peyton", 1980-1988, undated (Box 26)
  - "Sue Larish", 1986 (Box 26)
  - "Elaine Kunzi, Origin for the Poem Sighting / The Poem as Essay", 1981, undated (Box 26)
  - "A.T. Mann, Astrologer re: Elaine Kunzi & Portfolio Sales", 1973-1974, undated (Box 26)
  - "John Martin / Black Sparrow Press", 1979-1984 (Box 26)
  - "Twelve Trees Press", 1988-1990, undated (Box 26)
  - "GM: 100 Years Have Passed, Bk Mss Format", 1978 (Box 26)
  - "Jack Hirschman", 1972-1979 (Box 26)
  - "Emma Lovetere né Malanga", 1979-1984, undated (Box 26)
  - "The Found-Lost Poems of Willard Maas", 1971 (Box 26)
  - "Willard Maas Mss. Compiled by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 26)
  - "Chelsea #36", 1976-1977, undated (Box 26)
  - "Keith Richards' Orig. Music Industry Report on Marketing Stones LPs", undated (Box 26)
  - "Willard Maas on Edie Sedgwick", undated (Box 26)
  - "Diane Hersey / David Cudaback", 1990-1995 (Box 26)
  - "Jim Jacobs", 1977, undated (Box 26)
  - Supplementary Materials To Be Accessioned into Proper Folders, 1980-1988, undated (Box 26)
  - "Sara Vogeler", 1979-1982, undated (Box 26)
  - "Atlantic Avenue Railroad Tunnel Project - Bklyn", 1983-1990; 2 (Box 26)
  - "Deborah Krol Correspondence. Subject of GM Poem, 'How They Didn't Meet'", 1992, undated (Box 27)
  - "'Paintings I Have Not Seen by Deborah Krol' by Gerard Malanga", 1992 (Box 27)
  - "The Little Schoharie, Drafts 1992 (Deborah Krol)" (Box 27)
  - "Agnes Martin. Photocopies of Pgs. Transcribed by Deb Krol", undated (Box 27)
  - "7th Dream (without Deb Krol), 7:II:93", 1993 February 7 (Box 27)
  - "The Voice of Deb Krol in a 6th Dream, 21:VIII: 92", 1992 August 21 (Box 27)
  - "Fragment of a Dream - A 5th Dream - with Deb Krol, 12:VII:92", 1992 August 12 (Box 27)
  - "4th Dream with Deb Krol (and with Paul Bang and My Father)", 1992 July 28 (Box 27)
  - "3rd Dream with Deborah Krol, 23:VII:92", 1992 July 23 (Box 27)
  - "2nd Dream with Deb, 2:VII:92 (Deborah Krol)", 1992 July 2 (Box 27)
  - "First Dream with Deb, 28:V:92 (Deborah Krol)", 1992 May 28 (Box 27)
  - "Title: Metamorphosis of a Painting", 1992 June (Box 27)
  - "New Look Magazine - Paris", 1988-1992 (Box 27)
  - "Artist's Certificate", undated (Box 27)
  - "Major Surgery for Benign Tumor", 1988, undated (Box 27)
  - "Storage", 1990 (Box 27)
  - "Medical", 1990, undated (Box 27)
  - "G. Ray Hawkins Gallery, L.A.", 1988-1990 (Box 27)
  - "GM: Photography / 2 Anderson St.", 1990, undated (Box 27)
  - "Berkshire School / Poetry Reading", 1990 (Box 27)
  - "Canal 7 -Paris", 1991 (Box 27)
  - "Centre Georges Pompidou - 1990" (Box 27)
  - "Muses Marseille", 1990 (Box 27)
  - "Canal + / Channel 5, Paris", 1990 (Box 27)
  - "Vienna Filmmuseum, 1990" (Box 27)
  - "Canal 9 - Valencia, Spain", 1991 (Box 27)
  - "Bob Moore Cold-Drill", 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - "Luhring Augustine Gallery", 1990 (Box 27)
  - "Gabriella Sabatini", 1987-1995 (Box 27)
  - "Lita Hornick", 1990, undated (Box 27)
  - "The Bridge Magazine Rejection", 1990 (Box 27)
  - "Shanti Uppal Hippocrateslaan 55 Y624 VG Bergen Op Zoom, Holland", undated (Box 27)
  - "L'Orchestra in the Berkshires", 1990, undated (Box 27)
  - "Brent Sikkema Fine Arts GM w/ Allen Ginsberg", 1990 (Box 27)
  - "Bills, etc.", undated (Box 27)
  - "Albert Schweitzer Center", 1990-1992 (Box 27)
  - "Kristen Westad - Concept Photo", undated (Box 27)
  - "Norman Rockwell Museum", 1991 April (Box 27)
  - "Robert Motherwell, Obit", 1991 July 28 (Box 27)
  - "Wheeler Dixon: Proposal on Warhol Bk", 1990-1991, undated (Box 27)
  - "Writers Conference Possibilities", 1990, undated (Box 27)
  - "Julia Murphy", 1982 December 22 (Box 27)
  - "Berkshire Gas Company", 1990, undated (Box 27)
  - "Brendan Gill Interview by Nancy Hubshman w/ Gerard's Questions. Transcribed by Gerard", 1975, undated (Box 27)
  - "GM: 1991 Tax Return Prepared by Martin Deutsch" (Box 27)
  - "Bills: 2 Anderson St.", 1991, undated; 2 (Box 27)
  - "Unpaid Bills", 1990, undated; 2 (Box 27)
  - "Writers Conferences", 1981-1998; 2 (Box 28)
  - "Letterhead Stationary Collection, Incl. The Four Zous and the Paris Review", undated; 2 (Box 28)
  - "1990-91 Tax Debt", 1990-1993, undated; 3 (Box 28)
  - "Poetry Reading Solicitations 1977", 1976-1977, undated (Box 28)
  - "Translations & Translation Grants", undated (Box 28)
  - "Poetry Reading Solicitations 1982-83", 1976-1983 (Box 28)
  - "Poetry Reading Solicitations 1975-76", 1975-1976, undated (Box 28)
  - "Mark Weiss, Poet + Publisher", 1988, undated (Box 28)
  - "Ted Berrigan & Ron Padgett", 1964, undated (Box 28)
  - "Kevin Jeffrey Clarke 'In the Agora' Bk Mss Edited by G.M.", 1980 (Box 28)
  - "Gerald Hausman, Poet / Folklore Writer", undated (Box 28)
  - "Joseph Semenovich, Poet", undated (Box 28)
  - "Anne Cassinelli", 1986 (Box 28)
  - "Margaret Oyen", 1983, undated (Box 28)
  - "Gabriella Leventhal-Posner", 1986 (Box 28)
  - "Charles Giulano, Art + Music Critic", 1980-1982 (Box 28)
  - "Michael McCurdy / Penmaen Press", 1979-1992 (Box 28)
  - "Kathy Kaliban, One of Gerard's Models", 1982, undated (Box 28)
  - "Kristen Mäarten, One of Gerard's Models", 1981-1991 (Box 28)
  - "Phil Bleeth, Close Friend (Jasmine Bleeth's Dad)", 1972-1982 (Box 28)
  - "Rejection Letters", 1977-1988, undated (Box 28)
  - "James Brodey Poems, ca. Mid-1960s", 1959-1963, undated (Box 28)
  - "Christiane Heigl, Fashion Designer", 1986 (Box 28)
  - "Synn (Linda Stern), Artist", 1980-1986 (Box 29)
  - "Sylvia Pogorzalek, 'Pociao's Book Shop' Catalog w/ Listings of + Fotos by GM", 1979, undated (Box 29)
  - "Carl Weissner, German Poet + Translator", undated (Box 29)
  - "Jenny Robinson, Waitress", 1981 February 23 (Box 29)
  - "Timothy Baum, Poet / Art Dealer", 1978-1983 (Box 29)
  - "Daryl Hine / Poetry re Daniel Halpern", 1974, undated (Box 29)
  - "Louise Gluck, Poet", 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - "Paul Christensen, Poet", 1978-1980 (Box 29)
  - "Peter Dalano, Carpenter + Friend", 1978-1987, undated (Box 29)
  - "Ondine Cohane, One of Gerard's Models", 1982-1987, undated (Box 29)
  - "Celebrities, Incl. Peter Glenville", 1977-1982, undated (Box 29)
  - "Marcia Kresge, Poet", 1975-1977, undated (Box 29)
  - "Opale Harper", 1980-1981, undated (Box 29)
  - "Carola Fings", 1981, undated (Box 29)
  - "Andrei Codrescu, Poet", 1981-1985 (Box 29)
  - "Donna Brown, Poet", 1980 (Box 29)
  - "Patti Chambers, Actress", 1980-1983 (Box 29)
  - "Natalie Geary, Harvard Undergraduate", undated (Box 29)
  - "Amy Liu, Writer", 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - "Jerry Martin, Artist", 1981-1988, undated (Box 29)
  - "Julian Beck of the Living Theatre", 1961-1986, undated (Box 29)
  - "Vicki Perski", 1983-1988 (Box 29)
  - "Michael Reid", 1975, undated (Box 29)
  - "Eva Lee", 1987 (Box 29)
  - "Kathy Diener", 1975-1980, undated (Box 29)
  - "Manuel Auila Camacho López", 1988, undated (Box 29)
  - "Artists", 1977-1984, undated (Box 29)
  - "Gil Williams: Bellevue Press", 1982-1988 (Box 29)
  - "Charles Bernstein", 1983 April 20 (Box 29)
  - "Jessica Brackman", 1983-1988 (Box 29)
  - "Phoebe MacAdams. Lewis MacAdams' Wife at the Time", 1976, undated (Box 29)
  - "Queries & Fans", 1984-1988, undated (Box 29)
  - "Publishing House Rejections", 1976-1980 (Box 29)
  - "Peter Headington Corres(pondence)", 1983-1984, undated (Box 29)
  - "Peter Headington Interviews. Gerard Malanga, 2/12/83", 1983 (Box 29)
  - "Purchase Poetry Review", 1979-1980, undated (Box 29)
  - "Andy Warhol / Fred Hughes", 1976 (Box 29)
  - "Louis Waldon", 1980-1988 (Box 29)
  - "Billy Linich aka Billy Name", 1983-1988 (Box 29)
  - "Andy Warhol: John Rechy / GM Proposal", undated (Box 29)
  - "César Vallejo / Witter Bynner Award Application", undated (Box 29)
  - "Dr. Alfred Dorn / Poetry Society of America", undated (Box 29)
  - "Photo Memorabilia", undated (Box 29)
  - "Possessing the Secret", 1974 (Box 29)
  - "Dale Davis Correspondence", 1975-1988; 2 (Box 29)
  - "Editors / Publishers" Correspondence, 1977-1987; 3 (Box 30)
  - "Eban", 1986-1987, undated; 2 (Box 30)
  - "The Women in Gerard's Life", 1966-1987, undated; 4 (Box 30)
  - "The Pool Book", 1991; 2 (Box 30)
  - "GM: Swimming Pools Plaque Text / Drafts", undated (Box 30)
  - "Caliban Mag. Robert Moses Diptych / Foto & Text Proposal, Inc. One Specimen by Gerard Malanga", 1989 (Box 30)
  - "Robert Moses Exhibit. Grant Applications / Conservation Funding", 1988, undated (Box 30)
  - "Swimming Pools", 1989-1993, undated (Box 30)
  - "Simon & Schuster. Robert Moses Book Project Conceived & Edited by Gerard Malanga", 1987-1988, undated; 2 (Box 30)
  - "Faith Schuszler Grill. Interview on Her Father, Alajos Schuszler by Gerard Malanga", 1987, undated (Box 30)
  - "Robert Moses Book by G.M. Code: Citations, Sequence & Pagination", 1988, undated (Box 30)
  - "Fairchild Aerial Views etc", 1984-1987, undated (Box 30)
  - "Robert Moses GM's Research File", 1939-1991; 2 (Box 30)
  - "W.P.A. & W.P.A.-related, etc.", 1935-1995 (Box 31)
  - "Bathhouse History", 1912-1988 (Box 31)
  - "Henry J. Stern. Grant Proposal", undated (Box 31)
  - "Parks Dept. Properties and Related Tearsheets", 1941-1993, undated (Box 31)
  - "Gerard Malanga's Desk Name Plate at the NYC Parks Dept", undated (Box 31)
  - "Synopsis / Proposal. New York Parks & Recreation, 1934-1950: A Photographic Time-Line by Ethan Carr and Gerard Malanga", undated; 2 (Box 31)
  - City of New York Department of Parks and Recreation, 1989, undated (Box 31)
  - "Archives Job Applications, Etc.", 1986-1989 (Box 31)
  - "'Staten Island Views' Exhibit. Snug Harbor Cultural Ctr. 1987", undated; 2 (Box 31)
  - "1939 & 1964 N.Y. World's Fair", 1989-1989 (Box 31)
  - "1939 & 1964 World's Fairs - Plaque Texts, Guest Book", undated (Box 31)
  - "S.A.A. Certification", 1989 (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Gerard Malanga. Memorandums 1985-1988", 1986-1988; 2 (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Vendor Accts. 1986-1987", 1987, undated (Box 31)
  - "Playgrounds Exhibit. Curated by Ethan Carr / Photo Installation Design & Research by Gerard Malanga", 1986, undated (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Jeff Day Acct. Jan. 1988", 1988, undated (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Jeff Day Acct, July - Dec. 1987" (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Laura Rosen, Curator of Robert Moses Exhibit, Urban Center", undated (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Vendor: Stat Store, Inc.", 1987-1988 (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. C.C.F. / Cultural Council FDN Funding", 1987 (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept / Jeff Day Foto Lab", 1987 (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept / Phone Messages", undated (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept / Vendor Accts", 1987, undated (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept / Closed Accts", 1987-1988, undated (Box 31)
  - "NYC Parks Dept / Ephemera", 1985-1986, undated (Box 31)
  - "Parks Photo Archive Fugitive Photocopies", undated (Box 31)
  - "Vendor: Tiffany Communications. NYC Parks Dept re: Exhibitions", 1987 (Box 31)
  - "D.O.R.I.S.", 1986 (Box 31)
  - "Robert Moses Folio - Master Copy", 1968, undated (Box 31)
  - "Xerox Copy of Monuments Album", undated (Box 31)
  - "Coney Island", undated (Box 32)
  - "NYC Parks Department Photos", undated (Box 32)
  - "The Pool Book by Joseph Coplan + Gerard Malanga", 1981-1985 (Box 32)
  - "Outdoor Public Pools A.W.P.A. Photographic History 4-fold Announcements + Envelopes", undated (Box 32)
  - "W.P.A. Swimming Pools", 1986-1995 (Box 32)
  - "Astoria Pool Philippe Artru, Research", 1985-1986, undated (Box 32)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Directory 1985-186. Gerard's Personal Copy", undated (Box 32)
  - "The Pool Book Research by Joseph Coplan & Gerard Malanga", 1934-1986, undated (Box 32)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Photos, Ephemeral, etc.", 1986, undated (Box 32)
  - "Parks Dept. Press Clippings", 1986-1994 (Box 32)
  - "Timeless Images Preserved. Drafts to Article by Gerard Malanga re Parks Dept. Photo Archive", 1985, undated (Box 32)
  - "Parks Dept / Matters Dealing Directly w/ Gerard Malanga", 1986-1988, undated (Box 32)
  - "Parkways", 1995, undated (Box 32)
  - "Photo Conservation Research", 1953-1985, undated; 3 (Box 32)
  - "Parks Dept. Photo Collection Evaluation Report Authored by Gerard Malanga", 1981-1987 (Box 32)
  - "The Pool Book Proposal. Joseph Coplan & GM", undated (Box 32)
  - "Swimming Pool Exhibit Fold-out Announcement", undated (Box 32)
  - "The Pool Book Proposal", undated (Box 32)
  - "The Pool Book (Final Typescript) by Joseph Coplan & Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 32)
  - "M.I.T. Press Swimming Pool Bk", 1939, undated (Box 32)
  - "Letters to Publishers re Pool Book", 1985-1986, undated (Box 32)
  - Pools Exhibit, 1986 (Box 32)
  - "The Pool Book. A 50-Year History of New York City's Public Swimming Facilities by Joseph Coplan & Gerard Malanga", undated; 2 (Box 33)
  - "NYC Parks Dept. Publications", 1940-1994, undated; 4 (Box 33)
  - "Four in Focus Exhibit", 1987, undated (Box 33)
  - "Traveling Exhibitions", 1984-1988, undated (Box 33)
  - "Sports of the Parks Exhibition. Out-of-Pocket Expenses, Receipts. NYC Parks Dept. Transfile", 1988 April (Box 33)
  - "Carl Lucia - Olmsted CTR. Sports of the Parks", 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - "Sports of the Parks", 1988, undated (Box 33)
  - "A Tale of Two Fairs - Exhibit", 1987, undated (Box 33)
  - "Exhibit Panels for W.P.A. Architecture Conference / Urban CTR", undated (Box 33)
  - "Robert Moses on the Hudson: Riverside PK 50 Years Later 1937-1987 Exhibit", undated (Box 33)
  - "Park Harvests: Children's Farm Gardens Exhibition", undated (Box 33)
  - "Washington Heights - Inwood Views / Exhibitions", undated (Box 33)
  - "Annual Reports - Exhibit", undated (Box 33)
  - "Historic Landscapes Exhibition Curated by Gerard Malanga", 1987, undated (Box 33)
  - "Correspondence to Gerard Malanga at the NYC Parks Department, 1985-1988", 1950-1988, undated (Box 33)
  - "Project: Eight Delineations Towards A Photograpic Survey of the Parks System", 1984, undated (Box 33)
  - "Med-Plan Health Benefits - NYC Employee Benefits Program", 1986 (Box 33)
  - "Resignation Form / Malanga", 1986, undated (Box 33)
  - "This Is the Send-off Plaque Put Together for Gerard's Leave-taking from the Parks Dept. 1988"
  - "In View of the Riverdale. Launching the 'Views' Series Curated by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 33)
  - "In View of Riverdale. Curated by Gerard Malanga", undated; 2 (Box 33)
  - "Staten Island Views. Curated by Gerard Malanga at Snug Harbor Cultural Center, Staten Island", 1987, undated; 2 (Box 34)
  - "Outdoor Public Pools...", 1986, undated; 2 (Box 34)
  - "Talking Heads: Park Alumni 1934-1986. Curated by Gerard Malanga", 1986, undated (Box 34)
  - "The Golden Age of Parkways. Curated by Ethan Carr & Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 34)
  - "Evolution of the Playground. Curated by Ethan Carr: Park Historian. Photo Research: Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 34)
  - "Lower East Side Views Exhibit. Research Papers, etc.", 1986-1987, undated (Box 33)
  - "Lower East Side Views. Curated by Gerard Malanga", 1988, undated (Box 34)
  - "Coney Island Come Back. Exhibition Curated by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 34)
  - "Retrieval Records. Note: See Dale Davis's Request...", 1987, undated; 3 (Box 34)
  - "Retrieval Records", 1986-1988, undated; 3 (Box 34)
  - "Retrieval Records", 1985-1988, undated; 5 (Box 35)
  - "Self", 1982 (Box 35)
  - "Catching My Breath at St. Mark's Bookshop, 19:III:83 NYC", 1983, undated (Box 35)
  - "Transitional Poem", 1982, undated (Box 35)
  - "Moon-child [for Sara Matthiessen]", undated (Box 35)
  - "All Things Considered", 1980, undated (Box 35)
  - "Art Project: Mystery Woman, Ongoing Sighting", 1983 (Box 35)
  - "Topos / Mini-essay", 1976, undated (Box 35)
  - "March 20, 1979", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "'Briefe' Some Textual Evidence for Cynthia Genser", 1983, undated (Box 35)
  - "For Leslie Ullman, Untitled (Two Voices)", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "'Agere' (for Jeanne Oliver)", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "Michael Auder", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "'Seeing and Being Seen at a Distance,' for Annie Luce", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "'Forty-one Line Poem' for Sarah Greenleaf Whitier", 1980, undated (Box 35)
  - "Lore Poem (Tentative Title)", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "'Desideratum' [for Judy Scunics]", 1980, undated (Box 35)
  - "'This Is the End of Romance' (for Hoé)", 1978-1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "In Memory of Raya Nalywayko", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "Supplementary Notes Little Caesar #4 Interview w/ Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 35)
  - "'Turns' for Elaine Grove", 1978, undated (Box 35)
  - "2nd Typed Drafts / Letter to Leslie Ullman", 1979 (Box 35)
  - "Past Now or Ahead (Letter)", undated (Box 35)
  - "Notes for Leslie Ullman Letter", undated (Box 35)
  - "Drafts - Letter to Leslie Ullman", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - "The Body-and-Clothes Metaphor", 1981 October 14 (Box 35)
  - "The First Poem for 1982" (Box 35)
  - "Art Deco", 1982 December (Box 35)
  - "'Muthos' (for Amy)", 1983 (Box 35)
  - "History of the Photographers", undated (Box 35)
  - "To an Unknown Youth", 1981 (Box 35)
  - "Fucking", 1980 May 11 (Box 35)
  - "'Rain' (for Sara Matthiessen)", 1978 (Box 35)
  - "'The Lies' (for Diane Hersey)", 1974 (Box 35)
  - "'For Deirdre on New Year's Eve, 1982/83' (for Deirdre Goodwin)", undated (Box 35)
  - "Text / Thomas Meyar", 1980 (Box 35)
  - "Gretchen Husting, 1983" (Box 35)
  - "Sighting: Fri, March 13, 1981, 2:50 pm... (Sarah Walker)", undated (Box 35)
  - "Waking Up, Morning of the 11th Nov. '79", 1979 (Box 35)
  - "Dinkey Bird - Bennington Either Way", 1978 (Box 35)
  - "The Future Now, Afterword to Ten Years After: The Selected Benedetta Poems by Gerard Malanga 1977", undated (Box 35)
  - "'A Room in a Hotel' for Madge Bemiss", 1978 (Box 35)
  - "Occasions and Concerns for Peter Delano", 1978 (Box 35)
  - "To Be Included in File: 'This Is the End of Romance'", undated (Box 35)
  - "Making Up My Mind...", 1983 May 20 (Box 35)
  - "Cori", 1982 November 16 (Box 35)
  - "Poem of the Day", 1979, undated (Box 35)
  - " Little Caesar Interview with Gerard Malanga, Oct-Nov 1977" (Box 35)
  - "Fred Cook, Librarian, Bard College", 1976-1977 (Box 35)
  - "Charles Bukowski, Original Typed Drafts", undated (Box 35)
  - "The Ives Box", 1970, undated (Box 35)
  - "GM: Genealogies, Original Typescripts", 1979 October 14 (Box 35)
  - "J. Rutherford Willems Correspondence", 1974-1985, undated (Box 35)
  - "History and Architecture", circa 1989-1993 (Box 36)
  - "Jack Finney, Novelist", 1995 February 3 (Box 36)
  - "Lewis Mumford, Social Historian", undated (Box 36)
  - "Jacob Riis - Prints from Orig. Negatives", 1949-1991, undated (Box 36)
  - "Subways", 1990-1995, undated (Box 36)
  - "New York City", circa 1984-1994 (Box 36)
  - "Steamships / Oceanliners", 1974-1992, undated (Box 36)
  - "New York Historical Society", 1990-1995, undated (Box 36)
  - "Correspondence Dealing w/ Archives", 1992 October 1 (Box 36)
  - "F.P.G. / Brackman Archive Proposal", 1988-1989, undated (Box 36)
  - "Chuck Workman, Calliope Films re: Any Warhol", 1980s-1990s; 2 (Box 36)
  - "Charles Henri Ford & Indra Tamang", circa 1989-1996; 2 (Box 36)
  - "Federal Archives & Misc. Archives", circa 1985-1990; 2 (Box 36)
  - "Motion Picture Archives", 1976-1993, undated (Box 36)
  - "Archival Concentration", 1989-1993, undated (Box 36)
  - "Debbie Hess Norris, Conservator", 1993, undated (Box 36)
  - "S.A.A. / Society of American Archivists Correspondence", 1988-1990 (Box 36)
  - "Archival Matters", 1988-1990, undated (Box 36)